localpolicerecords.com 2016-11-02

# 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the LocalPoliceRecords.com and LocalPoliceRecords.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to LocalPoliceRecords.com include LocalPoliceRecords.com. The LocalPoliceRecords.com website is a Internet Marketing site. By using the LocalPoliceRecords.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

LocalPoliceRecords.com may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase LocalPoliceRecords.com’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. LocalPoliceRecords.com may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age and gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by LocalPoliceRecords.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the LocalPoliceRecords.com website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through LocalPoliceRecords.com’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

LocalPoliceRecords.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from LocalPoliceRecords.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. LocalPoliceRecords.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the LocalPoliceRecords.com website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

LocalPoliceRecords.com collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

LocalPoliceRecords.com may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from LocalPoliceRecords.com and its affiliates. LocalPoliceRecords.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

LocalPoliceRecords.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

LocalPoliceRecords.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. LocalPoliceRecords.com may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to LocalPoliceRecords.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

LocalPoliceRecords.com may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within LocalPoliceRecords.com, in order to determine what LocalPoliceRecords.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within LocalPoliceRecords.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

LocalPoliceRecords.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on LocalPoliceRecords.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of LocalPoliceRecords.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of LocalPoliceRecords.com, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

LocalPoliceRecords.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
LocalPoliceRecords.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from LocalPoliceRecords.com by contacting us here:  
– Web page: LocalPoliceRecords.com  
– Email: support@LocalPoliceRecords.com

**Changes to this Statement**  
LocalPoliceRecords.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. LocalPoliceRecords.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how LocalPoliceRecords.com is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
LocalPoliceRecords.com welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that LocalPoliceRecords.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact LocalPoliceRecords.com at:

LocalPoliceRecords.com  
820 Emerald St.  
St. Paul, Minnesota 55114

Email Address:  
Admin@LocalPoliceRecords.com

Effective as of November 13th 2012
